Papers of Morris K. Udall, 1920-1995
University of Arizona Library Special Collections
- Administrative Files, 1961-1990
  - Subject Files, 1961-1992
    - Subject Files, 91st Congress: Tax Reform. 1969-1970 (Box 652, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 91st Congress: Thank Yous. 1969 (Box 652, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 91st Congress: Visitors to Washington. 1969-1970 (Box 652, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 91st Congress: Volunteers. 1969-1970 (Box 652, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 91st Congress: Youth for Udall. 1969-1970 (Box 652, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Atlantic Union. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Baseball. 1971 (Box 653, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Blue Cross-Blue Shield. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Cantera, Sally. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Colleagues, Miscellaneous. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Colleagues, Special File. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Colleagues, Thanks for the Job of a Congressman. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Common Cause. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Condolences. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Congratulations. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 10-12)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Congressional Reform. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 13-16)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Contributions. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Dartmouth Conference. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Democrats, Arizona. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Delegation Meetings, Arizona. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 21-22)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Democratic National Committee. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Environment. 1971-1972 (Box 653, Folder 25-30)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Environmental Protection Act. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 1-3)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Farm Meeting. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Flags. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Federal Spending. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Federation of Nations. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Freshman Seminar. 1971 (Box 654, Folder 8-10)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Goldwater, Barry. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Hayden, Carl. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Industrial Development, Miscellaneous. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Industrial Development, Twin Plant Program. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Information Requests. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Interns, American Political Science Association. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Interns Accepted. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Israel Bond Drive. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Job Assistance. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 19-20)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Job Information, Miscellaneous. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Jobs Summer. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Leadership, King Article. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Mexican-Americans. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Members of Congress for Peace Through Law. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 25-26)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Military Goofs. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Miscellaneous. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 28-29)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: 1971-1972 (Box 654)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Mount Lemmon Property Owners. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Fredrick Palmer, Personal. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 31)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Patronage. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 32)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Patriots. 1971-1972 (Box 654, Folder 33)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Steiger, Sam. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 1-2)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Pen Pals. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 3-4)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Plaudits. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Politics, Miscellaneous. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 6-9)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Pollution Trends. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Population. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 11-12)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Priorities. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Publications. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 14-16)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Quotations. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Radicals. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Rail Strike. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Recommendations. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 20-21)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Redistricting. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Referred. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Resolutions and Platforms. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Right to Work. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Speeches. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Sponsorships. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Testimonial Dinner. 1971 (Box 655, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Thank Yous. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Urban Problems. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: Visitors to Washington. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 31)
    - Subject Files, 92nd Congress: White House Conference on Youth. 1971-1972 (Box 655, Folder 32)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Abortion. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Advocates. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 2-12)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Agnew, Spiro. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Amnesty. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Appointments. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Arizona Democratic Party. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Arizona Politics. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 17-18)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Campaign Reform. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Colleagues. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Condolences. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Congratulations. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 22-23)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Congressional Reform. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Contributions from Morris K. Udall. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Democrats, Arizona. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1973 (Box 656, Folder 27-28)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Democratic National Committee. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Energy. 1973-1974 (Box 656, Folder 30-32)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Environment. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Fannin. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Federal Spending. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Freshman Seminar. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 4-6)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Fundraising. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Goldwater. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 8-10)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Impeachment. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 11-12)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Inaugural. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Industrial Development, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Industrial Development, Electric Car. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Inflation. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Information Requests. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Interns. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 18-19)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Mexican-Americans. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Patriots. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Patronage. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Pen Pals. 1973-1974 (Box 657, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Pen Pals, Massey. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Plaudits. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Politics, Miscellaneous. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 3-5)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Pollock, Williams Recall Election. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Population. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Priorities. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Recommendations. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Redistricting. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Soviet Union, Jews. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Soviet Union, Trade. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Speakers. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 13-14)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Sponsorship. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Sports. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Sports, U.S. Olympic Committee. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Sports, White House-Congress on Amateur Athletics. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Visitors to Washington. 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 93rd Congress: Watergate (Four Bound Volumes). 1973-1974 (Box 658, Folder 20-24)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Watergate (Four Bound Volumes). 1975-1976 (Box 659)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Abortion. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Aging. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Amnesty. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Bolles, Dan. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Colleagues. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Condolences. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Congratulations. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 7-9)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Congressional Reform. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Conlan, John. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Contributions. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 12-13)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Crime. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Democratic National Committee. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Democratic Steering and Policy Committee. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: District Office. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Economy. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 19-21)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Energy. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 22-23)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Environment. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 24-25)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Federal Spending. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 26-27)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Freshman Seminar. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Fugate, Paul. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Goldwater. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Group Research Report. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 31)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Industrial Development. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 32-33)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Inflation. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 34)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Interns. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 35-39)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Job Assistance. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 40-42)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Information Requests. 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 43)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Media. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 1-2)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Mexican-Americans. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Newsletter. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Patriots. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 5-6)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Patronage. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 7-8)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Pen Pals. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 9-11)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Plaudits. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Politics. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 13-14)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Polls. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Population. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 16-17)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Recommendations. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 18-19)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Resolutions. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 20-21)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Sponsorships. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: United Nations. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Visitors to Washington. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 94th Congress: Women's Issues. 1975-1976 (Box 661, Folder 25-26)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Arizona, Bussing. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Arizona, Politics. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 2-3)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Arizona, Sonora-Desert Museum. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Arizona Trips. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Carter Presidency. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Civil Service. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Colleagues. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Congratulations. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Contributions. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Contributions. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 11-14)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Energy. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Grants. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Heyl, TC. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Industrial Development. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Jojoba. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 20-21)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Manzo Area Council. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Mexican-Americans. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Patriots. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Office Organization. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Opinion Polls. 1977-1978 (Box 662, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Pen Pals. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 1-5)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Pettine, Ronald J. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Plaudits. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 7-8)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Politics. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 9-10)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Professional Air Traffic Controllers. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Resolutions. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Richey, Thomas. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: San Carlos Reservoir Bill. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Solar Energy. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 15-16)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Speakers. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Sponsorships. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 18-19)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Thank Yous. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Twin Plant, Mexico. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Tucson. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Vision Quest. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: War Control Planners, Inc. (Kurtz, Howard). 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 95th Congress: Women's Issues. 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Abortion. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Arizona Hospital Association. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Arizona Politics. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Budget. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Center for Urban & Environmental Studies. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Colleagues. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Congressional Comfort Caucus. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Contributions. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Copper. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Democratic Caucus. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: J. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Economy. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Endorsements. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Energy. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Federal Budget. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Grants. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Guayule and Jojoba. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Gun Control. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Industrial Development. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Inflation. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Kennedy Endorsement. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 965th Congress: Media. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Members of Congress for Peace Through Law. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Memberships. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Mexican-Americans. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Murphy, Lewis. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Papago, Tucson Foreign Trade Zone. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Patriots. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Patronage. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Kudos. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 30)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Pen Pals. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 31-32)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Plaudits. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 33)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Politics. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 34-35)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Presidential Campaign. 1980 (Box 664, Folder 36)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Presidential Campaign, Kennedy. 1979-1980 (Box 664, Folder 37)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Small Businesses. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 1-19)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Sponsorships. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Steel Caucus. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Stump, Robert. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Vision Quest. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 23-24)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Wilderness. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Wilson, Charles H. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 26)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Women's Issues. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 27)
    - Subject Files, 96th Congress: Youth Advisory Council. 1979-1980 (Box 665, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Aging, Alien Workers. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Arizona Budget. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Arizona Politics. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: CAP, Tucson Aqueduct. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Colleagues. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Copper. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: DeConcini, Dennis. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 7-8)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Democratic National Committee. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Democratic Steering/Policy Committee. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: District Profile. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Economy. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Elderly. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Endorsements. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Foreign Affairs. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Grants. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Guayule. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Hoover Dam Lawsuit. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Indian Water Rights. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Industrial Development. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Interns. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Legal Issues. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Media. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Nuclear Licensing. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Nuclear Safety Regulations. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 24a)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: O'Connor, Sandra Day. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Pen Pals. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 26-27)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Plaudits. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 28)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: Politics. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 29)
    - Subject Files, 97th Congress: President, State of the Union Address. 1981-1982 (Box 666, Folder 30)